<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Certification Prep by Microsoft Press and Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/microsoft-certification-prep-microsoft-press-and-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Microsoft certification prep made easy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed on your Microsoft certification exams with this bundle of prep courses from Microsoft Press and Pearson. Inside this 20+ library, you’ll get expert insights from courses like <em>Exam Ref AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals, 3rd Edition</em>, <em>Exam Ref AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator, 2nd Edition</em>, <em>Exam Ref MS-102 Microsoft 365 Administrator</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional testing for your Microsoft certifications. Get this great bundle and help support Hello World with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scythe and More by Neal Shusterman</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/scythe-and-more-neal-shusterman-books</link>
      <description>Addicting page-turners by Neal Shusterman</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the worlds and stories of Neal Shusterman! This 15+ book collection is highlighted by Shusterman’s standout novel <em>Scythe</em>—a gripping depiction of a world free of death. Other top titles include <em>Dry</em>, <em>Toll</em>, <em>Thunderhead</em>, and more from one of young adult fiction’s most renowned authors. Lose yourself in this expansive library, and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Comics, Manga, &amp; Animation by Walter Foster</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mastering-comics-manga-animation-walter-foster-books</link>
      <description>Master comics, manga, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Curious about drawing? Sharpen your existing skills or start drawing from square one with our latest bundle. Get ebooks like <em>Big School of Drawing Manga, Comics & Fantasy</em>, <em>How to Draw Kawaii Manga Characters</em>, <em>Cartoon Animation</em>, and <em>Cartooning Made Easy: Circle, Triangle, Square</em>. There’s no limit to what you can create, plus, your purchase helps support The Hero Initiative.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a Python Expert by Pearson Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/become-python-expert-pearson-books-encore</link>
      <description>Sage Python advice from the pros</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you’re a seasoned pro or a budding coder looking to cut your teeth in web dev, data science, or AI engineering, this bundle of Python books from Pearson will bolster your command of this indispensable programming language! <em>Effective Python</em> will teach you tips and tricks, straight from Google Python guru Brett Slakin, to help you get the most out of your code. Aimed at experienced developers, <em>Deitel: Python for Programmers</em> provides hands-on exercises focusing on deep learning, big data, and other exciting applications. <em>Learn Python 3 the Hard Way</em> gives you a rigorous crash course where you’ll create working code regardless of your level. Get all these and more, and help support Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math for Programmers 2024 by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-for-programmers-2024-manning-books</link>
      <description>Strengthen your math muscles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Algorithms. Robotics. Graphics. Games. Data analysis. AI. Mathematics is the foundation of computer science. What better way to wrap up 2024 than expanding your coding toolkit with math skills that will make you a better programmer–no matter what you’re building next! The Manning Publications Math for Programmers Humble Bundle includes books on everything from basic statistics and data analysis, to data science and deep learning, to geometry, calculus, and Bayesian theory. This amazing bundle will keep you learning and growing for years to come! With the books’ included registration codes, Manning enhances your experience with liveBook including: all book formats online; bookmarking; highlighting; a reader’s forum; liveTest (self testing throughout the text); AI functionality; and, more.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Wizard of Earthsea and More by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/wizard-earthsea-and-more-ursula-k-le-guin-books</link>
      <description>Magical titles for your home library </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the worlds and stories of author Ursula K. Le Guin with another great Humble Book Bundle! This 25+ book collection features <em>A Wizard of Earthsea</em>, <em>Tehanu</em>, <em>Tales from Earthsea</em>, and more from one of speculative fiction’s most renowned authors. Your purchase helps support Literary Arts, a nonprofit located within Le Guin’s community. Lose yourself in this expansive library today.<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available on Kobo.com. To access them, create or log in to your Kobo.com account. Please note that the content redemption deadline is December 15, 2027 at 11:00 AM PDT.</em></strong></a> ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G.I. JOE Deck-Building Game Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/gi-joe-deckbuilding-game-collection-books</link>
      <description>Build a deck of awesome G.I. Joe Heroes</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for a deck-building game experience like no other—join the war against the nefarious group, Cobra, in the <em>G.I. Joe Deck-Building Game</em>. Create a team of elite comrades and lead them to battle against your friends. Joe, Snake Eyes, and more are at your disposal… How will you use them? Get the <em>G.I. JOE Deck-Building Game Cold Snap Expansion</em>, <em>G.I. JOE Deck-Building Game Shadow of the Serpent Expansion</em> and other physical goods shipped to your home. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the charity of your choice!</p> <p><a style="color: #ef9741;"> Shipping is only available in the US, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand. </a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition &#34;Happy Birthday, Remaster!&#34; Bundle from Paizo Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-happy-birthday-remaster-bundle-from-paizo-inc-books</link>
      <description>Be the legendary hero of Golarion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your friends for endless adventure with the Ultimate Pathfinder Second Edition Bundle from Paizo Inc.! Experience the best way to play <em>Pathfinder</em> with this amazing bundle, which includes rulebooks, new scenarios, a bestiary, flip-mats, and campaign resources for <em>Pathfinder GM Core</em>, <em>Pathfinder Second Edition Beginner Box: Remastered Edition</em>, and <em>Pathfinder Player Core</em>, and more. Tabletop RPGs have never been this fun—get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together while supporting ComicBooks For Kids! with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Cookbooks 2024 by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/coding-cookbooks-2024-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Pocket guides &amp; references for programmers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for the recipe to coding success? Pick up these concise, easy-to-use digital guides and references from O’Reilly! This bundle features the latest updates to popular courses like <em>Machine Learning with Python Cookbook</em>, and <em>Terraform Cookbook</em>. The books in this bundle cover a wide range of topics, including programming with Qiskit, Q#, C#, SQL, and PowerShell; understanding machine learning; using Linux; and lots more. Plus, your purchase helps support Code for America. Update your library with these new courses today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G.I. JOE Roleplaying Game by Renegade Game Studio</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/gi-joe-roleplaying-game-renegade-game-studio-books</link>
      <description>Battle Cobra Commander with friends</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from Renegade Game Studios! This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains expansions, add ons, and new campaign resources for the <em>G.I. JOE Roleplaying Game</em>. Plus, you get an awesome G.I. JOE Roleplaying Game Cobra Dice Set including a journal, dice bag, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support The Movember Foundation with your purchase! <br><br><a style="color:#EF9741">Shipping of physical items is limited to addresses in the US, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand.</a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Ultimate Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-ultimate-collection-books</link>
      <description>A TMNT comic bundle? Cowabunga dude!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the totally classic <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</em> comic series in this bundle from publisher IDW. Read 25+ comic books featuring everyone’s favorite ninja turtles—Michelangelo, Leonardo, Raphael, and Donatello! Get far out titles like <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Last Ronin Director's Cut</em>, <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Ultimate Collection, Vol. 1</em>, <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Armageddon Game</em>, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase! <br><br><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7th Sea RPG Collection by Chaosium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/7th-sea-rpg-collection-chaosium-books</link>
      <description>The perfect mix of swashbuckling and sorcery</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with a staple from the tabletop role-playing game genre—<em>7th Sea</em>. This collection of books, campaigns, and resources will have your merry gang of crewmen swashbuckling and spellcasting in no time. Get amazing loot like <em>7th Sea: Lands of Gold and Fire</em>, <em>7th Sea: The New World</em>, <em>7th Sea: Land of 1000 Nations</em>, and more. Explore this sea-worthy bundle from Chaosium Inc. plus, your purchase will support Oceana!</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming MEGA Bundle 2024 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/programming-mega-bundle-2024-packt-books</link>
      <description>Upgrade your functional programming knowledge</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with the Programming Mega Bundle 2024! This amazing library features 15+ courses specifically curated with emerging trends and industry standards in mind. Get great courses from publisher, Packt like Learn LLVM 17, System Design Guide for Software Professionals, and Build Your Own Programming Language. Grow your career possibilities with courses for novice coders and seasoned pros, and help support Code.org with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowrun Fiction Mega Bundle by Catalyst Game Labs</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shadowrun-fiction-mega-bundle-catalyst-game-labs-books</link>
      <description>A WORLD OF MAGIC, MACHINES, AND MAYHEM!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Experience the dark, dystopian future of <em>Shadowrun</em>, where magic and technology collide! Whether you're jumping in for the first time or an experienced shadowrunner, there's something for any fan of the Sixth World in this massive ebook library of dozens of novels and anthologies, including <em>Dark Synergy</em>, <em>Magic, Machines, and Mayhem</em>, and <em>Shadow Borders</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the BINC Foundation, a charity dedicated to assisting booksellers and comic sellers in times of financial crisis.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>