<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 06:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Math for Programmers 2024 by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-for-programmers-2024-manning-books</link>
      <description>Strengthen your math muscles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with this bundle of ebooks! Get <em>Solve Any Data Analysis Problem</em>, <em>Graph Algorithms for Data Science</em>, <em>Math and Architectures of Deep Learning</em>, and more with this library of 20+ programming guides from Manning. Get resources for  novice coders and seasoned pros in growing your career, and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Wizard of Earthsea and More by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/wizard-earthsea-and-more-ursula-k-le-guin-books</link>
      <description>Magical titles for your home library </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the worlds and stories of author Ursula K. Le Guin with another great Humble Book Bundle! This 25+ book collection features <em>A Wizard of Earthsea</em>, <em>Tehanu</em>, <em>Tales from Earthsea</em>, and more from one of speculative fiction’s most renowned authors. Your purchase helps support Literary Arts, a nonprofit located within Le Guin’s community. Lose yourself in this expansive library today.<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available on Kobo.com. To access them, create or log in to your Kobo.com account. Please note that the content redemption deadline is December 15, 2027 at 11:00 AM PDT.</em></strong></a> ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition &#34;Happy Birthday, Remaster!&#34; Bundle from Paizo Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-happy-birthday-remaster-bundle-from-paizo-inc-books</link>
      <description>Be the legendary hero of Golarion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your friends for endless adventure with the Ultimate Pathfinder Second Edition Bundle from Paizo Inc.! Experience the best way to play <em>Pathfinder</em> with this amazing bundle, which includes rulebooks, new scenarios, a bestiary, flip-mats, and campaign resources for <em>Pathfinder GM Core</em>, <em>Pathfinder Second Edition Beginner Box: Remastered Edition</em>, and <em>Pathfinder Player Core</em>, and more. Tabletop RPGs have never been this fun—get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together while supporting ComicBooks For Kids! with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G.I. JOE Deck-Building Game Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/gi-joe-deckbuilding-game-collection-books</link>
      <description>Build a deck of awesome G.I. Joe Heroes</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for a deck-building game experience like no other—join the war against the nefarious group, Cobra, in the <em>G.I. Joe Deck-Building Game</em>. Create a team of elite comrades and lead them to battle against your friends. Joe, Snake Eyes, and more are at your disposal… How will you use them? Get the <em>G.I. JOE Deck-Building Game Cold Snap Expansion</em>, <em>G.I. JOE Deck-Building Game Shadow of the Serpent Expansion</em> and other physical goods shipped to your home. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the charity of your choice!</p> <p><a style="color: #ef9741;"> Shipping is only available in the US, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand. </a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Cookbooks 2024 by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/coding-cookbooks-2024-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Pocket guides &amp; references for programmers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for the recipe to coding success? Pick up these concise, easy-to-use digital guides and references from O’Reilly! This bundle features the latest updates to popular courses like <em>Machine Learning with Python Cookbook</em>, and <em>Tableau Desktop Cookbook: Quick & Simple Recipes to Help You Navigate Tableau Desktop</em>. The books in this bundle cover a wide range of topics, including programming with Qiskit, Q#, C#, SQL, and PowerShell; understanding machine learning; using Linux; and lots more. Plus, your purchase helps support Code for America. Update your library with these new courses today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Ultimate Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-ultimate-collection-books</link>
      <description>A TMNT comic bundle? Cowabunga dude!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the totally classic <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</em> comic series in this bundle from publisher IDW. Read 25+ comic books featuring everyone’s favorite ninja turtles—Michelangelo, Leonardo, Raphael, and Donatello! Get far out titles like <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Last Ronin Director's Cut</em>, <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Ultimate Collection, Vol. 1</em>, <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Armageddon Game</em>, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase! <br><br><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G.I. JOE Roleplaying Game by Renegade Game Studio</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/gi-joe-roleplaying-game-renegade-game-studio-books</link>
      <description>Battle Cobra Commander with friends</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from Renegade Game Studios! This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains expansions, add ons, and new campaign resources for the <em>G.I. JOE Roleplaying Game</em>. Plus, you get an awesome G.I. JOE Roleplaying Game Cobra Dice Set including a journal, dice bag, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support The Movember Foundation with your purchase! <br><br><a style="color:#EF9741">Shipping of physical items is limited to addresses in the US, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand.</a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7th Sea RPG Collection by Chaosium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/7th-sea-rpg-collection-chaosium-books</link>
      <description>The perfect mix of swashbuckling and sorcery</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with a staple from the tabletop role-playing game genre—<em>7th Sea</em>. This collection of books, campaigns, and resources will have your merry gang of crewmen swashbuckling and spellcasting in no time. Get amazing loot like <em>7th Sea: Lands of Gold and Fire</em>, <em>7th Sea: The New World</em>, <em>7th Sea: Land of 1000 Nations</em>, and more. Explore this sea-worthy bundle from Chaosium Inc. plus, your purchase will support Oceana!</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Histories by Thom Hartmann</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hidden-histories-thom-hartmann-books</link>
      <description>The Secret History of America</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[What better time to learn the secret history of the United States of America? Get the complete 10-book collection of Thom Hartmann’s Hidden Histories. Learn about The War on Voting, American Democracy, and Monopolies! Thrill to tales of The Supreme Court and the Betrayal of America; Guns and the Second Amendment; and more! Pay what you want for 10 amazing books and help support the Worldreader with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming MEGA Bundle 2024 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/programming-mega-bundle-2024-packt-books</link>
      <description>Upgrade your functional programming knowledge</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with the Programming Mega Bundle 2024! This amazing library features 15+ courses specifically curated with emerging trends and industry standards in mind. Get great courses from publisher, Packt like Learn LLVM 17, System Design Guide for Software Professionals, and Build Your Own Programming Language. Grow your career possibilities with courses for novice coders and seasoned pros, and help support Code.org with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowrun Fiction Mega Bundle by Catalyst Game Labs</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shadowrun-fiction-mega-bundle-catalyst-game-labs-books</link>
      <description>A WORLD OF MAGIC, MACHINES, AND MAYHEM!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Experience the dark, dystopian future of <em>Shadowrun</em>, where magic and technology collide! Whether you're jumping in for the first time or an experienced shadowrunner, there's something for any fan of the Sixth World in this massive ebook library of dozens of novels and anthologies, including <em>Dark Synergy</em>, <em>Magic, Machines, and Mayhem</em>, and <em>Shadow Borders</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the BINC Foundation, a charity dedicated to assisting booksellers and comic sellers in times of financial crisis.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hammer by Jeff Lemire from Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/black-hammer-jeff-lemire-from-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Strike while Black Hammer is hot!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned <em>Black Hammer</em> comic series with this bundle from Dark Horse Comics! Get 20+ titles including <em>Black Hammer Volume 1: Secret Origins</em>, <em>Black Hammer: Visions</em>, featuring amazing guest writers &amp; artists including Scott Snyder, Patton Oswalt, Chip Zdarsky, Mariko Tamaki and many more, and Eisner and GLAAD Media Award-nominated <em>Barbalien</em>, to name just a few. Follow the lives and times of former heroes, now outcast, as they exist in a now hero-less society. The full bundle also includes two acclaimed Jeff Lemire graphic novels not related to <em>Black Hammer: Mazebook</em> and <em>Berserker Unbound</em>. Read the tales of <em>Black Hammer</em> and support The Hero Initiative with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shells and Scripting for Seasoned Admins by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shells-and-scripting-for-seasoned-admins-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Shells and scripting for seasoned admins</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with this bundle of ebooks! Learn PowerShell, scripting, Linux, and more with this library of 10+ courses from O’Reilly. Programs like <em>Efficient Linux at the Command Line: Boost Your Command-Line Skills</em>, <em>Learning the Bash Shell: Unix Shell Programming</em>, and <em>Efficient Linux at the Command Line: Boost Your Command-Line Skills</em> are great for novice coders and seasoned pros alike. Get this amazing bundle and help support Code for America with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/warhammer-fantasy-roleplay</link>
      <description>Venture back to the Old World</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for a new <em>Warhammer</em> adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from acclaimed game company, Cubicle 7! This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for <em>Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay</em> like <em>Winds of Magic</em>, <em>Imperial Zoo</em>, <em>Salzenmund: City of Salt and Silver</em>, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support Children’s Health Ireland with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>