<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity and Forensics by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-and-forensics-packt-books</link>
      <description>Arm yourself for cyber-warfare </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed in defending your networks, websites, and more with this bundle of in-depth cybersecurity lessons from Packt. Inside this 15+ course library, you’ll get expert insights from industry-leading courses including <em>Cyber Warfare - Truth, Tactics, and Strategies</em>, <em>Practical Cybersecurity Architecture</em>, <em>iOS Forensics for Investigators</em>, and more! Deepen your understanding of the detection and prevention of cyber attacks, whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spies vs Vampires: The complete Night&#39;s Black Agents &amp; Dracula Dossier Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/spies-vs-vampires-complete-nights-black-agents-dracula-dossier-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Burned spies face the horrors of the night</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Powered by the GUMSHOE system, the Night’s Black Agents RPG lets you play hyper-competent spies fighting a conspiracy led by vampires. This bundle features rules, adventures and expansions for the <em>Night’s Black Agents</em> RPG, including the epic <em>Dracula Dossier</em> campaign. In this campaign, you must track down and face the ultimate threat - Dracula himself! The Dossier offers an updated version of Stoker’s masterpiece and adds new letters and recordings, diary entries, and documents suppressed by Her Majesty’s Government, plus a <em>Director’s Handbook</em> filled with locations and leads to let your players hunt their greatest adversary. From Transylvania to London, the hunt is on!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stitch &amp; Bitch by Insight Editions</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/stitch-bitch-insight-editions-books</link>
      <description>Really flippin’ cute stitched designs</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Feeling a little frustrated—do you need to work out some aggression? Then our newest bundle from Insight Editions is for you. The Stitch & Bitch Bundle is our edgiest and funniest crafts bundle ever! Get ebooks like <em>Maybe Swearing Will Help: Relax and Curse Your Ass Off In Cross-Stitch</em>, <em>Festive As F*ck: Subversive Cross-Stitch For the Holidays</em>, <em>Crochet Amigurumi For Every Occasion: 21 Easy Projects to Celebrate Life's Happy Moments</em>, and more! Plus, your purchase helps NatureBridge!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unseen Struggles: Living with Anxiety, Depression, ADHD, and More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/unseen-struggles-living-with-anxiety-depression-adhd-and-more-books</link>
      <description>Mental health teachings from top professionals </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get ebooks from top professionals to help you manage your depression, anxiety, ADHD, and other mental diagnoses. You’re not alone—and this bundle is designed to help you feel seen and to show that we all struggle inside sometimes. Learn new techniques from titles like <em>Why Smart People Hurt</em>, <em>Hack Your Anxiety</em>, <em>Depression Hates a Moving Target</em>, <em>Mini ADHD Coach</em>, and more. Manage your unseen struggles and help support Active Minds with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic the Hedgehog Comics Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sonic-hedgehog-comics-collection-books</link>
      <description>Collect comics with the Blue Blur</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[He’s the fastest thing alive, and the star of some amazing comics. Sonic the Hedgehog spotlights our latest comics bundle. This bursting library contains 10+ issues and volumes of adventures featuring Tails, Knuckles, and other iconic characters from the Sonic Universe. Get fan favorite titles like <em>Sonic the Hedgehog 30th Anniversary Celebration: The Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>Sonic the Hedgehog, Vol. 1: Fallout</em>, <em>Sonic the Hedgehog, Vol. 2: The Fate of Dr. Eggman</em>, and more! You better catch up and get this great bundle today, and help support Children's Miracle Network with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT Manager&#39;s Toolkit by Taylor &amp; Francis</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/it-managers-toolkit-taylor-francis-books</link>
      <description>Captain a tight &amp; secure IT ship</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to lead in information technology with this bundle of elite courses from Taylor & Francis. Inside this 25+ curriculum, you’ll get expert insights from courses like <em>The IoT Architect's Guide to Attainable Security and Privacy</em>, <em>Big Data for Big Decisions: Building a Data-Driven Organization</em>, <em>Evolving Toolbox for Complex Project Management</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a newer manager or a seasoned professional, and help support Every Child a Reader with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manara, Moebius, and the Metabaron by Humanoids</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/metal-hurlant-moebius-and-metabaron-humanoids-books</link>
      <description>Fresh comics with fiercely independent styles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in an awesome comics collection featuring <em>Metal Hurlant: Selected Works</em>, <em>The Incal Vol. 1-6</em>, <em>The Metabaron Vol. 1-6</em>, and more! Feel the power of turning the digital page on a gripping story with a warm drink on a cool winter day and get our latest comic book bundle by Humanoids Publishing today! Since their founding in the early 1970s, Humanoids Publishing has embodied creative innovation, a fiercely independent spirit, and a drive to break new ground within the medium. Get 50+ titles, and help support the Freedom to Read Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellboy Universe Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hellboy-universe-megabundle-books</link>
      <description>A hellishly good Hellboy Megabundle </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned <em>Hellboy</em> comic series in this Megabundle from Dark Horse Comics! Get 25+ novels, comics, and graphic novels exploring the rich, dark, hilarious and action-packed world of the demonic superhero, Hellboy. This Megabundle features red hot Hellboy titles like <em>Hellboy and the B.P.R.D: 1952-1956</em>, Mike Mignola's <em>Hellboy 2023</em>, <em>Abe Sapien Volume 1: The Drowning</em>, and more! Explore the expansive Hellboy Universe and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>