<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 10:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Programming MEGA Bundle 2024 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/programming-mega-bundle-2024-packt-books</link>
      <description>Upgrade your functional programming knowledge</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with the Programming Mega Bundle 2024! This amazing library features 15+ courses specifically curated with emerging trends and industry standards in mind. Get great courses from publisher, Packt like Learn LLVM 17, System Design Guide for Software Professionals, and Build Your Own Programming Language. Grow your career possibilities with courses for novice coders and seasoned pros, and help support Code.org with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowrun Fiction Mega Bundle by Catalyst Game Labs</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shadowrun-fiction-mega-bundle-catalyst-game-labs-books</link>
      <description>A WORLD OF MAGIC, MACHINES, AND MAYHEM!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Experience the dark, dystopian future of <em>Shadowrun</em>, where magic and technology collide! Whether you're jumping in for the first time or an experienced shadowrunner, there's something for any fan of the Sixth World in this massive ebook library of dozens of novels and anthologies, including <em>Dark Synergy</em>, <em>Magic, Machines, and Mayhem</em>, and <em>Shadow Borders</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the BINC Foundation, a charity dedicated to assisting booksellers and comic sellers in times of financial crisis.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hammer by Jeff Lemire from Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/black-hammer-jeff-lemire-from-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Strike while Black Hammer is hot!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned <em>Black Hammer</em> comic series with this bundle from Dark Horse Comics! Get 20+ titles including <em>Black Hammer Volume 1: Secret Origins</em>, <em>Black Hammer: Visions</em>, featuring amazing guest writers &amp; artists including Scott Snyder, Patton Oswalt, Chip Zdarsky, Mariko Tamaki and many more, and Eisner and GLAAD Media Award-nominated <em>Barbalien</em>, to name just a few. Follow the lives and times of former heroes, now outcast, as they exist in a now hero-less society. The full bundle also includes two acclaimed Jeff Lemire graphic novels not related to <em>Black Hammer: Mazebook</em> and <em>Berserker Unbound</em>. Read the tales of <em>Black Hammer</em> and support The Hero Initiative with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shells and Scripting for Seasoned Admins by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shells-and-scripting-for-seasoned-admins-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Shells and scripting for seasoned admins</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with this bundle of ebooks! Learn PowerShell, scripting, Linux, and more with this library of 10+ courses from O’Reilly. Programs like <em>Efficient Linux at the Command Line: Boost Your Command-Line Skills</em>, <em>Learning the Bash Shell: Unix Shell Programming</em>, and <em>Efficient Linux at the Command Line: Boost Your Command-Line Skills</em> are great for novice coders and seasoned pros alike. Get this amazing bundle and help support Code for America with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Age and Mass Effect Comics by Dark Horse ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dragon-age-and-mass-effect-comics-dark-horse-encore-books</link>
      <description>Explore the worlds of Dragon Age &amp; Mass Effect comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The masterfully realized universes of famed game maker BioWare come alive on the page in this collection of <em>Dragon Age</em> and <em>Mass Effect</em> comics from Dark Horse! Prime yourself for high adventure with <em>Dragon Age: The Missing</em>, the comic story that leads into <em>Dragon Age: The Veilguard</em>, the upcoming fourth installment in the beloved RPG series. Get into Commander Shepard’s offscreen adventures in <em>Mass Effect Volume 1: Redemption</em>, which takes place after the events of the revered <em>Mass Effect 2</em>. Get more than 15 exciting <em>Dragon Age</em> and <em>Mass Effect</em> volumes in this bundle, and support Child’s Play with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutants &amp; Masterminds 3e RPG Collection by Green Ronin</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mutants-masterminds-rpg-collection-green-ronin-books</link>
      <description>Get Freedom City, Power Profiles, Rogues Gallery and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for epic adventures with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from Green Ronin. Answer the hero's call and defend the globe from nefarious masterminds. This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for <em>Mutants & Masterminds Third Edition</em>, including awesome add-ons like <em>Freedom City</em>, <em>Rogues Gallery</em>, and more. Get everything you need to embark on a heroic journey together, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!<br/><br/><p style="color: #ef9741;"><b><u>The content in this bundle is redeemed through the DriveThruRPG website.</b></u></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/warhammer-fantasy-roleplay</link>
      <description>Venture back to the Old World</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for a new <em>Warhammer</em> adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from acclaimed game company, Cubicle 7! This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for <em>Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay</em> like <em>Winds of Magic</em>, <em>Imperial Zoo</em>, <em>Salzenmund: City of Salt and Silver</em>, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support Children’s Health Ireland with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Sysadmin and DevOps by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/windows-sysadmin-and-devops-packt-books</link>
      <description>Super SysAdmin &amp; DevOps Windows tools</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and gain the knowledge you need to succeed in system administration and development operations for Windows with this bundle of insightful courses by Packt. Inside this amazing curriculum, you’ll get expert insights on mastering Windows Server 2022, Windows security and hardening, PowerShell scripting, and more. Deepen your understanding of SysAdmin and DevOps whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official Marvel, Star Wars, and Disney Cookbooks by Insight Editions</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/official-marvel-star-wars-disney-cookbooks-insight-editions-books</link>
      <description>Cook with a little bit of magic</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to cook, bake, and mix up amazing foods and drinks with this fantastic bundle of Marvel, Star Wars, and Disney cookbooks! Inside this collection of over 15 culinary titles, you’ll find delectable books like <em>The Nightmare Before Christmas: The Official Baking Cookbook</em>, <em>Marvel: Spider-Man: The Official Cookbook</em>, and <em>Star Wars: The Ultimate Cookbook</em>. Recreate dishes craved by beloved characters or try original recipes inspired by heroes, princesses, and more. Level up your skills in the kitchen while supporting First Book with your purchase!<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival &amp; Bushcraft How-To Guides by Skyhorse Publishing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/survival-bushcraft-howto-guides-skyhorse-publishing-books</link>
      <description>Could you survive the wilds?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Survival & Bushcraft Bundle by Skyhorse Publishing is the ultimate how-to guide on thriving in the wilderness and beyond. Get amazing outdoor survival titles like <em>Art of Bushcraft: A Field Guide to Preserving Traditional Skills and Reconnecting with Nature</em>, <em>Surviving the Coming War: A Guide to Wartime Survival for Civilians</em>, <em>Mini Farming Bible: The Complete Guide to Self-Sufficiency on 1/4 Acre</em>, and more! Learn potentially lifesaving techniques and support the BINC Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Cthulhu by Chaosium, Inc. ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/call-cthulhu-chaosium-inc-encore-books</link>
      <description>Invite eldritch terror to your table</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bring a taste of terror to your game nights with this bundle from Chaosium, complete with everything you need to run the dreaded (yet beloved) <em>Call of Cthulhu</em> RPG system! On top of the <em>Call of Cthulhu Starter Set</em>, you’ll get the <em>Investigator Handbook</em>, replete with expanded rules for creating player characters, as well as the <em>Keeper Rulebook</em>, brimming with all the information you need to keep things orderly as your table descends into madness. You’ll also get tons of adventures, including some aimed at first-time game masters, as well as entire campaigns! Pay what you want for over 25 books and game aids for this seminal RPG and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Darkness: Month of Darkness 2024 Bundle by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/world-darkness-month-darkness-2024-bundle-renegade-game-studios-books</link>
      <description>Enter the mysterious World of Darkness</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate the Month of Darkness with our World of Darkness Bundle by Renegade Game Studios—featuring the <em>Vampire: The Masquerade 5th Edition Core Rulebook</em>, <em>Hunter: The Reckoning 5th Edition Core Rulebook</em>, <em>Werewolf: The Apocalypse 5th Edition Core Rulebook</em>, and more! Get everything you need to embark on these epic journeys with your friends, and support the charity of your choice with your purchase. Don’t miss out on this spooky collection of great TTRPG games! <br/> <br/>Note: Due to limited physical quantities, the $40 tier is no longer available.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>