<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 09:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate RPG Guides by Adams Media Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-rpg-guides-adams-media-holiday-encore-2024-books</link>
      <description>Level up your role-playing</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Back for a Very Humble Holiday encore…Make your campaigns more epic, your heroes more mythic, and your game sessions more fun for the whole party with these books from Adams Media! This TTRPG treasure trove features 20+ digital guides to worldbuilding, coming up with great characters, concocting compelling challenges, being a legendary host, and lots more. Explore a library for players, DMs, and anyone who loves the art and craft of role-playing, and help support Worldreader with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fandom &amp; Pop Culture Cookbooks Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fandom-pop-culture-cookbooks-books-encore</link>
      <description>Whip up magical culinary treats</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bring magic, whimsy, and wonder to your dinner table with this bundle of cookbooks inspired by some of pop culture’s most iconic stories and worlds. The <em>Unofficial Harry Potter Cookbook</em> serves up spellbinding recipes that will transport you straight to the Hogwarts dining hall. With the <em>Unofficial Disney Parks Cookbook</em>, you can recreate the iconic tastes of your favorite Disney Park treats, from Mickey Pretzels to Luke Skywalker’s Blue Milk. The <em>Studio Ghibli Cookbook</em> reveals how to concoct the mouthwatering meals seen in Miyazaki’s mesmerizing worlds. Pay what you want for this delectable library of 30+ books and help support charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT Manager&#39;s Toolkit by Taylor &amp; Francis</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/it-managers-toolkit-taylor-francis-books</link>
      <description>Captain a tight &amp; secure IT ship</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to lead in information technology with this bundle of elite courses from Taylor & Francis. Inside this 25+ curriculum, you’ll get expert insights from courses like <em>The IoT Architect's Guide to Attainable Security and Privacy</em>, <em>Big Data for Big Decisions: Building a Data-Driven Organization</em>, <em>Evolving Toolbox for Complex Project Management</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a newer manager or a seasoned professional, and help support Every Child a Reader with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manara, Moebius, and the Metabaron by Humanoids</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/metal-hurlant-moebius-and-metabaron-humanoids-books</link>
      <description>Fresh comics with fiercely independent styles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in an awesome comics collection featuring <em>Metal Hurlant: Selected Works</em>, <em>The Incal Vol. 1-6</em>, <em>The Metabaron Vol. 1-6</em>, and more! Feel the power of turning the digital page on a gripping story with a warm drink on a cool winter day and get our latest comic book bundle by Humanoids Publishing today! Since their founding in the early 1970s, Humanoids Publishing has embodied creative innovation, a fiercely independent spirit, and a drive to break new ground within the medium. Get 50+ titles, and help support the Freedom to Read Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellboy Universe Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hellboy-universe-megabundle-books</link>
      <description>A hellishly good Hellboy Megabundle </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned <em>Hellboy</em> comic series in this Megabundle from Dark Horse Comics! Get 25+ novels, comics, and graphic novels exploring the rich, dark, hilarious and action-packed world of the demonic superhero, Hellboy. This Megabundle features red hot Hellboy titles like <em>Hellboy and the B.P.R.D: 1952-1956</em>, Mike Mignola's <em>Hellboy 2023</em>, <em>Abe Sapien Volume 1: The Drowning</em>, and more! Explore the expansive Hellboy Universe and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools for Data Engineers by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/tools-for-data-engineers-packt-books</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Data Engineer’s Cookbook </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Strengthen your skills and knowledge in data engineering with the Ultimate Data Engineer’s Cookbook Bundle of ebooks Packt. Inside this 20+ book library, you’ll get expert insights from courses like <em>Data Governance Handbook</em>, <em>Databricks Certified Associate Developer for Apache Spark Using Python</em>, <em>The Ultimate Guide to Snowpark</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Coral Guardian with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Wellness &amp; Happiness Toolkit by New World Library</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/your-wellness-happiness-toolkit-new-world-library-books</link>
      <description>Prioritize your happiness and wellness</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to prioritize your wellness and happiness with our newest bundle from New World Library! Get ebooks like <em>Career Self-Care</em>, <em>Healing with Nature</em>, <em>Say it Out Loud</em>, and <em>Panic Free</em>. You are important and you’re worth treating yourself right—get the bundle that can help you become the best version of yourself. Plus, your purchase helps support World Central Kitchen!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magical Worlds of V. E. Schwab: The Invisible Life of Addie LaRue, The Shades of Magic series, and More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/magical-worlds-v-e-schwab-invisible-life-addie-larue-shades-magic-series-and-more-books</link>
      <description>Discover modern award-winning fiction</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into the imaginative worlds and captivating stories of #1 New York Times bestselling author V.E. Schwab with this literary bundle! This multi-book collection features bestselling titles like <em>The Invisible Life of Addie LaRue</em>, <em>A Darker Shade of Magic</em>, <em>The Fragile Threads of Power</em>, and more. Amazing modern fiction is being written every year—expand your personal library and discover some of the best new novels on the market. Lose yourself in this expansive collection, all while supporting The Trevor Project with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking 2024 by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hacking-2024-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Stop hackers by understanding hacking</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your hacking and cyber security skills with this bursting tech bundle from No Starch! Learn from top hacking courses like <em>Hacks, Leaks, and Revelations</em>, <em>Windows Security Internals</em>, <em>Practical IoT Hacking</em>, and more! Get 15+ guides and courses to help you better understand the intricacies of hacking so you can better defend yourself from future cyber attacks. Get professional level resources for both novice and seasoned hackers, and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation and ACLU Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books About Games by Boss Fight Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/books-about-games-boss-fight-games-books</link>
      <description>The ultimate library of video game history</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the detailed history, production process, and secrets of your favorite titles. This 30+ book collection features ebooks on gaming’s greatest games like <em>GoldenEye 007: Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>Red Dead Redemption</em>, <em>Final Fantasy VI</em>, <em>Majora's Mask</em>, and more from Boss Fight Books. This massive bundle will teach you about games that shaped the trajectory of the industry. Lose yourself in this expansive library, and help support Against Malaria Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free League RPG Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/free-league-rpg-mega-bundle-books</link>
      <description>So many TTRPGs, so little time!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from Free League Publishing! Our Free League RPG Mega Bundle features a wide variety of TTRPG games for you to enjoy with your friends. Get explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for <em>Forbidden Lands RPG</em>, <em>Tales from the Loop RPG</em>, <em>Mutant: Year Zero</em>, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition &#34;Happy Birthday, Remaster!&#34; Bundle from Paizo Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-happy-birthday-remaster-bundle-from-paizo-inc-books</link>
      <description>Be the legendary hero of Golarion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your friends for endless adventure with the Ultimate Pathfinder Second Edition Bundle from Paizo Inc.! Experience the best way to play <em>Pathfinder</em> with this amazing bundle, which includes rulebooks, new scenarios, a bestiary, flip-mats, and campaign resources for <em>Pathfinder GM Core</em>, <em>Pathfinder Second Edition Beginner Box: Remastered Edition</em>, and <em>Pathfinder Player Core</em>, and more. Tabletop RPGs have never been this fun—get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together while supporting ComicBooks For Kids! with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>