<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Future Games Show Discovery Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/future-games-show-discovery-encore</link>
      <description>Future Games Show legends</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Relive the Future Games Show Summer Showcase—which was live on June 8th—with this bundle of games packed with hits that graced the show in years past! Brace yourself for <em>Gloomwood</em>, a haunting immersive sim set in a Victorian-inspired world teeming with secrets and dread. Become the star of a deadly retro future <em>Truman Show</em>-style reality show in the thrilling 2.5D adventure <em>American Arcadia</em>. Set sail on a cooperative roguelite romp across hazardous, monster-infested seas in <em>Ship of Fools</em>. Pay what you want for all these, plus 5 other great games, and help support It Gets Better and Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metroidvania Mania Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/metroidvania-mania-encore</link>
      <description>Unlock abilities, progress, repeat</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Rejoice in the thrills of exploration and discovery with this bundle of Metroidvania games, featuring some of the genre's most exceptional recent entries. In the critically acclaimed <em>9 Years of Shadows</em>, you'll explore a stunning, handcrafted world that’s been drained of all color while wielding amazing powers and taking in a star-studded soundtrack. Lose yourself in the sprawling alien world of <em>Axiom Verge 2</em>, the boundary-pushing sequel to the fan-favorite sci-fi game (that’s also included in this bundle!). Experience the genre at its most subversive in <em>Cookie Cutter</em>, full of dark humor, brutal combat, and some of the finest hand-drawn art the genre has ever seen. Get all these games and more—7 in total—and help support the Global Foodbanking Network with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesome Snack 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wholesome-snack-2024</link>
      <description>Cute, calm, and curated for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LKIt8AAnqKI?si=cA2oeDZE61prISx0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Looking to unwind with some cozy games? The Wholesome Snack Bundle celebrates the Wholesome Snack indie game showcase and offers a selection of titles brimming with charm. Step into the paws of an adventurous feline in <em>Little Kitty, Big City</em>. Immerse yourself in a world where farming meets magic in <em>Fae Farm</em>, and relax to the soothing vibes of <em>Spirit City: Lofi Sessions</em>. These games—and more—invite you to explore the softer, kinder side of gaming and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!<br><br>Wholesome Snack: The Game Awards Edition returns December 10, 2024 starting at 12:00 PM Pacific, 3:00 PM Eastern. The digital showcase will be presented via <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/WholesomeGames" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> and <a href="http://twitch.tv/wholesome_games" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitch</a> livestreams.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rawcember to Remember</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/rawcember-to-remember</link>
      <description>RAWcember to Remember is here!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready to play something new? The world of indie gaming is vast, deep, and bursting with amazing titles. Publishers like Raw Fury release amazing indie games that span a variety of genres—from serious shooters to musical puzzle games. Get awesome indie titles like <em>Dome Keeper Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>Kingdom Two Crowns: Norse Lands Edition</em>, <em>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</em>, and more with Raw Fury’s RAWcember to Remember bundle! Experience new games and help support Save the Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>