<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 04:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Telltale Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/the-telltale-collection</link>
      <description>Captivating storytelling meets amazing gameplay</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore captivating renditions of your favorite franchises with our Telltale Collection. Create your own adventures set within the worlds of <em>Batman</em>, <em>The Walking Dead</em>, <em>The Expanse</em>, and more. The Telltale Collection features iconic titles like <em>The Expanse: A Telltale Series</em>, <em>The Walking Dead: The Telltale Definitive Series</em>, and <em>Batman: The Enemy Within</em>. Lose yourself in Telltale Games’ signature choose-your-own-adventure style today and help support Save The Children with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Get Tactical with Kalypso</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/lets-get-tactical-with-kalypso</link>
      <description>Let’s get tactical with Kalypso</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the games of Kalypso with our Let’s Get Tactical Bundle! Packed with outstanding real-time strategy and role-playing games, this library highlights some of the best titles in the genres. Battle through hoards of demonic enemies in <em>Disciples: Liberation</em>, build your own sick dungeons in <em>Dungeons 3 Complete Collection</em>, wage war from the comfort of your computer in <em>Sudden Strike 4</em>, and more. Play amazing games and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2K Presents: The Sid Meier Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/2k-presents-sid-meier-collection</link>
      <description>Build the greatest empire ever</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the outstanding games and worlds of <em>Sid Meier</em> with our latest bundle! <em>Sid Meier’s Civilization VI</em> headlines this engaging library of great games—choose from a variety of civilizations and lead your people to prosperity. Enjoy awesome add ons to <em>Sid Meier’s Civilization VI</em> like the Leader Pass, the New Frontier Pass, Beyond Earth - The Collection, and more! Start your adventure today and help support Covenant House and The Michael J. Fox Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuneScape: Devourer</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/runescape-devourer</link>
      <description>Spooky seasonal fun for RuneScape</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the immersive world of Gielinor with the new <em>RuneScape: Devourer</em> Bundle. Experience the long-running MMOrpg and its new story quest complete with special in-game gear! Unbox up to 4 Umbral Chests, 420 RuneCoins, 100 Keys, 10 Medium Protean Packs, and more. Plus, one month of RuneScape membership is included with your purchase. Pay what you want to level up your <em>RuneScape</em> experience, and help support SpecialEffect with your purchase!!<br/><br/> <em>Buyers who already own cosmetic items will not receive duplicates.</em> <br/><br/>Restrictions:<br/><em>Bundle purchase grants single key that will redeem all items on one Runescape account. Limit one key redemption per account.</em><br/><br/><i><span>Ironman characters will only receive the membership, cosmetic rewards and RuneCoins.<br/><br/></span></i><i>Players with mobile membership can claim either bundle, but membership will only be used once their mobile membership has ended.<br/><br/>Players can only purchase one Humble code (either the Premium or Standard Bundle, not both).</i><br/><br/><em><span style="color: #ff9900;">Accounts with two and a half years or more of membership stacked will not be able to&nbsp;redeem.</span></em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>