<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 10:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>RuneScape: Devourer</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/runescape-devourer</link>
      <description>Spooky seasonal fun for RuneScape</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the immersive world of Gielinor with the new <em>RuneScape: Devourer</em> Bundle. Experience the long-running MMOrpg and its new story quest complete with special in-game gear! Unbox up to 4 Umbral Chests, 420 RuneCoins, 100 Keys, 10 Medium Protean Packs, and more. Plus, one month of RuneScape membership is included with your purchase. Pay what you want to level up your <em>RuneScape</em> experience, and help support SpecialEffect with your purchase!!<br/><br/> <em>Buyers who already own cosmetic items will not receive duplicates.</em> <br/><br/>Restrictions:<br/><em>Bundle purchase grants single key that will redeem all items on one Runescape account. Limit one key redemption per account.</em><br/><br/><i><span>Ironman characters will only receive the membership, cosmetic rewards and RuneCoins.<br/><br/></span></i><i>Players with mobile membership can claim either bundle, but membership will only be used once their mobile membership has ended.<br/><br/>Players can only purchase one Humble code (either the Premium or Standard Bundle, not both).</i><br/><br/><em><span style="color: #ff9900;">Accounts with two and a half years or more of membership stacked will not be able to&nbsp;redeem.</span></em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation Zero: The Ultimate Resistance</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/generation-zero-ultimate-resistance</link>
      <description>Revolt and survive dystopian Sweden</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into the world of <em>Generation Zero</em> with our fully loaded game bundle! This stealth-action shooter sees players battling against futuristic mechanical enemies in a world inspired by the Swedish Cold War era. Enjoy the core game plus the complete collection of DLCs and add-ons like the <em>Alpine Unrest</em>, <em>FNIX Rising</em>, and June 2024’s Heavy Weapons Pack. Pay what you want for the ultimate <em>Generation Zero</em> experience, and help support Girls Who Code and Special Effect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Pictures and Little Nightmares: A Halloween Horror Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/dark-pictures-and-little-nightmares-halloween-horror-collection</link>
      <description>Prepare for Halloween with the ultimate horror bundle!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into The Dark Pictures Anthology, where every choice could end in a gruesome death. From the chilling cult of <em>The Devil in Me</em> to an ancient Sumerian temple in <em>House of Ashes</em>, take a chilling journey through the darkest corners of human terror. Then, face your fears in the sinister world of <em>Little Nightmares</em> and uncover the dark secrets of the Nowhere in <em>Little Nightmares II</em>. Unlock your nightmares and support a brighter future at Covenant House and Breakthrough T1D with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/house-flipper</link>
      <description>Live your House Flipper fantasy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get your screwdriver, new tiles, and knowhow with this value-packed <em>House Flipper</em> bundle—featuring the core game, an amazing collection of add-ons, and DLC. Fire up the farm or pets DLC and create sprawling farms with the most adorable creatures around. Tackle a variety of home renovation scenarios and sell your investments for big profits in this addicting home-simulator title. Pay what you want for the ultimate <em>House Flipper</em> bundle and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microids Mystery Menagerie</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/microids-mystery-menagerie</link>
      <description>Beloved books &amp; films made playable</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Work through the clues of all four modern Agatha Christie PC titles featuring famous literary detective Hercule Poirot, plus more mysteries from Microids. Get amazing titles from the <em>Syberia</em> series, and contemporary classics <em>Alfred Hitchcock - Vertigo</em> and <em>Blacksad: Under the Skin</em>! Explore, interrogate, and fend for your life while piecing together the puzzle of what is really going on. Trust no one! Start investigating today and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atari: Recharged Retro Revival</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/atari-recharged-retro-revival</link>
      <description>Atari classics for a new generation </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the iconic legacy of Atari with our latest game bundle! Their pioneering work helped shape video games as we know them today. Take an interactive journey through 50 years of over 100 playable video games with <em>Atari 50</em>, and experience 10 more classic titles Recharged &amp; reimagined for a new generation. Play amazing games like <em>Asteroids: Recharged</em>, <em>Breakout: Recharged</em>, <em>Yars: Recharged</em>, and more! Pay what you want and help support Take This with your purchase!<br/><p style="color: #ef9741;"><i>"Our team at the Atari family of games recognizes and supports the vital role that Take This plays in decreasing the stigma and increasing the support for mental health services for the enthusiast game community and within the game industry itself."</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>