<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 05:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Night, Deadly Night: A GOG Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/silent-night-deadly-night-gog-bundle</link>
      <description>Silent night, deadly night</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become one with the night—vanquish your foes silently and efficiently with this bundle of amazing stealth and action games! The Silent Night, Deadly Night Bundle features heart-pumping titles like <em>Aragami 2</em>; <em>Slave Zero X</em>; <em>Furi</em>; and more! Add jaw-dropping stealth action titles to your personal libraries today—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesome Snack 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wholesome-snack-2024</link>
      <description>Cute, calm, and curated for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LKIt8AAnqKI?si=cA2oeDZE61prISx0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Looking to unwind with some cozy games? The Wholesome Snack Bundle celebrates the Wholesome Snack indie game showcase and offers a selection of titles brimming with charm. Step into the paws of an adventurous feline in <em>Little Kitty, Big City</em>. Immerse yourself in a world where farming meets magic in <em>Fae Farm</em>, and relax to the soothing vibes of <em>Spirit City: Lofi Sessions</em>. These games—and more—invite you to explore the softer, kinder side of gaming and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!<br><br>Wholesome Snack: The Game Awards Edition returns December 10, 2024 starting at 12:00 PM Pacific, 3:00 PM Eastern. The digital showcase will be presented via <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/WholesomeGames" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> and <a href="http://twitch.tv/wholesome_games" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitch</a> livestreams.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>