<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 23:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Beamdog &amp; Owlcat: RPG Masters Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/beamdog-owlcat-rpg-masters-encore</link>
      <description>Killer RPGs from the modern masters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Killer RPGs from the modern masters.</strong> CRPG fans, this is the one you’ve been waiting for! Owlcat and Beamdog are responsible for some of the finest RPGs of the last decade—now’s your chance to snag both their entire CRPG catalogs in a single epic bundle! Highlights include:</p> <ul> <li><em>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</em>: Explore the grimdark future like never before and take on Mankind’s most horrifying enemies in this story-rich and tactically rigorous classical RPG.</li> <li><em>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous</em>: Shake the very foundations of Golarion in this sprawling RPG, where you’ll amass nigh godlike power and lead vast armies against an infernal threat.&nbsp;</li> <li><em>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous Season Pass 1 and 2:&nbsp;</em>If the main game wasn't enough roleplaying goodness, great news, we've included both season passes containing six additional content packs adding a slew of new character options, spells, and storylines.</li> </ul> <p>Get all these games and more—including classics like <em>Baldur’s Gate: Enhanced Edition</em>, <em>Neverwinter Nights: Complete Adventures</em>, and many more. Plus, your purchase helps support the Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund!</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board Game Night with Dire Wolf &amp; Friends Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/board-game-night-with-dire-wolf-digital-friends-encore</link>
      <description>Legendary board games on your screen</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Some of the best board games of recent years are coming to your digital domain in this eclectic bundle from some of the finest purveyors out there! Whether you’re in the mood for breezy beer and pretzels gaming or chunky competitive strategy, this bundle has an exquisitely crafted digital board game for you. Choose a faction and conquer Arrakis by any means necessary in <em>Dune: Imperium</em>. Create an efficient engine of avian productivity in the bird-tastic <em>Wingspan</em>. Turn the red planet green with fancy tech and deft dealings in <em>Terraforming Mars</em>. Get 9 games total (plus some DLC) and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back with a Vengeance: The Best of Boomer Shooters Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/back-with-vengeance-best-boomer-shooters-encore</link>
      <description>Return to simpler times</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Treat yourself to a shotgun blast from the past with this bundle of boomer shooters, sure to help you blow off steam while bathing you in gibs! You’ll get the slick, hyperviolent <em>Ultrakill</em> that rewards you for slaying with frenetic style. Also included are a host of other titles inspired by the old school greats, including the dark, Lovecraft-inspired <em>Forgive Me Father 2</em>, and <em>Turbo Overkill</em>, whose over-the-top action is excessive even by boomer shooter standards. Pay what you want for this bundle of 7 awesome games and help support Child’s Play and the Trevor Project! <br><br><em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the games are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesome Snack 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wholesome-snack-2024</link>
      <description>Cute, calm, and curated for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LKIt8AAnqKI?si=cA2oeDZE61prISx0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Looking to unwind with some cozy games? The Wholesome Snack Bundle celebrates the Wholesome Snack indie game showcase and offers a selection of titles brimming with charm. Step into the paws of an adventurous feline in <em>Little Kitty, Big City</em>. Immerse yourself in a world where farming meets magic in <em>Fae Farm</em>, and relax to the soothing vibes of <em>Spirit City: Lofi Sessions</em>. These games—and more—invite you to explore the softer, kinder side of gaming and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!<br><br>Wholesome Snack: The Game Awards Edition returns December 10, 2024 starting at 12:00 PM Pacific, 3:00 PM Eastern. The digital showcase will be presented via <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/WholesomeGames" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> and <a href="http://twitch.tv/wholesome_games" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitch</a> livestreams.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Classics Black Friday Humble Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/disney-classics-black-friday</link>
      <description>A vault full of Disney Classics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Journey into the wonderful past with these beloved Disney franchises. Build your favorite heroes in LEGO games featuring Star Wars, Indiana Jones, and the Pirates of the Caribbean. Speaking of pirates, join Guybrush Threepwood in a collection of Monkey Island adventures or travel to a galaxy far, far away with Star Wars Knights of the Old Republic and Republic Commando. Delve into a deep catalog of Disney Classics and help support the Starlight Children's Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rawcember to Remember</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/rawcember-to-remember</link>
      <description>RAWcember to Remember is here!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready to play something new? The world of indie gaming is vast, deep, and bursting with amazing titles. Publishers like Raw Fury release amazing indie games that span a variety of genres—from serious shooters to musical puzzle games. Get awesome indie titles like <em>Dome Keeper Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>Kingdom Two Crowns: Norse Lands Edition</em>, <em>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</em>, and more with Raw Fury’s RAWcember to Remember bundle! Experience new games and help support Save the Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-Fi Shooters</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/scifi-shooters</link>
      <description>Dark and futuristic sci-fi shooters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[From the depths of space to a galaxy far, far away. Get award-winning and timeless sci-fi shooters with this bundle of awesome games! Use the Force in <em>Star Wars: Dark Forces Remaster</em>, experience an all-time classic in 2023’s <em>System Shock</em>, send demons back to hell in <em>DOOM</em>, and more. Play some of the greatest titles of the genre, and help support One Tree Planted and Cool Effect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>