<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rawcember to Remember</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/rawcember-to-remember</link>
      <description>RAWcember to Remember is here!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready to play something new? The world of indie gaming is vast, deep, and bursting with amazing titles. Publishers like Raw Fury release amazing indie games that span a variety of genres—from serious shooters to musical puzzle games. Get awesome indie titles like <em>Dome Keeper Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>Kingdom Two Crowns: Norse Lands Edition</em>, <em>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</em>, and more with Raw Fury’s RAWcember to Remember bundle! Experience new games and help support Save the Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-Fi Shooters</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/scifi-shooters</link>
      <description>Dark and futuristic sci-fi shooters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[From the depths of space to a galaxy far, far away. Get award-winning and timeless sci-fi shooters with this bundle of awesome games! Use the Force in <em>Star Wars: Dark Forces Remaster</em>, experience an all-time classic in 2023’s <em>System Shock</em>, send demons back to hell in <em>DOOM</em>, and more. Play some of the greatest titles of the genre, and help support One Tree Planted and Cool Effect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Telltale Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/the-telltale-collection</link>
      <description>Captivating storytelling meets amazing gameplay</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore captivating renditions of your favorite franchises with our Telltale Collection. Create your own adventures set within the worlds of <em>Batman</em>, <em>The Walking Dead</em>, <em>The Expanse</em>, and more. The Telltale Collection features iconic titles like <em>The Expanse: A Telltale Series</em>, <em>The Walking Dead: The Telltale Definitive Series</em>, and <em>Batman: The Enemy Within</em>. Lose yourself in Telltale Games’ signature choose-your-own-adventure style today and help support Save The Children with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>