<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 15:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Speedrunning with Awesome GDQ</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/speedrunning-with-awesome-gdq</link>
      <description>How fast can you go?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Race to the finish at breakneck speed in our Speedrunning with Awesome Games Done Quick Bundle! This amazing bundle features standout speed-running titles like the ones featured at the Games Done Quick—a semiannual charity event that celebrates the passion and community of Speed Runners. These games are perfect for savvy speed runners and those new to the hobby like <em>Have a Nice Death</em>, <em>Ori and the Blind Forest</em>, <em>Sonic Lost World</em>, and more. Explore the world of speed running and support the Prevent Cancer Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New You: Communication &amp; Meditation</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/new-years-resolution-learn-new-skill-encore</link>
      <description>Unlock your New Year’s achievements</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[As you explore new languages with Influent—and have fun in the process—with this bundle of games designed to help you learn! Embark on a mystical quest in the typing RPG adventure <em>Nanotale: Typing Chronicles</em>. Build vocabulary and practice pronunciation as you explore the world of <em>Influent</em>. Grow a world through mindfulness in <em>PLAYNE: The Meditation Game</em>. Plus, help support Prevent Cancer Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Night, Deadly Night: A GOG Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/silent-night-deadly-night-gog-bundle</link>
      <description>Silent night, deadly night</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become one with the night—vanquish your foes silently and efficiently with this bundle of amazing stealth and action games! The Silent Night, Deadly Night Bundle features heart-pumping titles like <em>Aragami 2</em>; <em>Slave Zero X</em>; <em>Furi</em>; and more! Add jaw-dropping stealth action titles to your personal libraries today—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>