<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Shapelab Creator&#39;s Kit: 3D &amp; VR Sculpting Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/shapelab-creators-kit-software</link>
      <description>3D design at your fingertips</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create high-quality 3D models from the palms of your hands with the Shapelab 3D Bundle from Leopoly! This high-quality collection features a <em>Shapelab 2024</em> license, a voucher for the 2025 edition, and more! Create 3D dragons, dinosaurs, and other mysterious creatures with this awesome bundle. Get the assets you need to help bring your creations to life, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Award Winning Assets - The Crown Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/naturemanufacture-awardwinningassets-thecrowncollection-software</link>
      <description>Nature made easy with amazing assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers—build rich worlds, unique environments, and lush landscapes with Award Winning Assets - The Crown Collection. This bundle from NatureManufacture, winner of Unity's publisher of the year award, features environments, characters, meshes, models, animations, music, SFX, and more! Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Starlight Children's Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAPS Extravaganza Revisited 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/maps-extravaganza-revisited-2024-software</link>
      <description>Bring your fantasy worlds to life</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Design maps for your own tabletop campaigns, fantasy settings, and more! This bundle includes everything you need to create stunning, print-worthy works of art that will bring your worlds to life. Get powerful software like Campaign Cartographer 3+ (including a Lifetime License), City Designer 3, Dungeon Designer 3, Tome of Ultimate Mapping, and more. Unlock a treasury that will take your tabletop games and fantasy stories to the next level, and help support Save the Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monument Studios: TTRPG Audio Compendium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/monument-studios-ttrpg-audio-compendium-software</link>
      <description>A bundle bursting with amazing music</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with this bundle of royalty-free sounds from Monument Studios! This massive library features loops, samples, one-shots, instruments, and others for a variety of genres & styles. Amazing collections like <em>Battle Music Vol 1 & 2</em>, <em>Fantasy Music Vol 1</em>, <em>Cinematic Hits</em>, and more. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2024 Learn Unity Game Development Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2024-learn-unity-game-development-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Get started in Unity today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to create games with Unity with these online courses from GameDev.tv! This comprehensive curriculum covers core skills and advanced concepts for the powerful and popular development platform. Find out how to make a 2D RPG combat system, VR experience, or turn-based strategy game. Get trained up on visual scripting, multiplayer, network coding, and more. Level up your Unity game dev skills, and help support Oceana with your purchase!<br><p>GameDev.tv have spent the last decade working with world class instructors to create the perfect learning experience for game development. Join our global community of over 2 million students and start making your own games today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev Market: Best of 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/gamedev-market-best-2024-software</link>
      <description>75+ assets to create endlessly</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build your worlds with this bundle of 75+ assets from GameDev Market! This massive collection features a diverse range of high-quality assets, including detailed tilesets, unique character sprites, huge music and sound effects packs, and so much more. Perfect for indie developers and seasoned studios alike, this bundle has everything you need to help bring your game to life, and help support The Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plugin Boutique Music Production Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/plugin-boutique-music-production-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Boutique plugin tunes and tones</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with this bundle of exceptional sounds! This massive library features loops, samples, and instruments for a variety of genres & styles. Gain access to professional quality software like <em>WaveOsc</em>, <em>FilterMod</em>, <em>ResDelay</em>, and more. Perfect for novices or professionals—get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Game Asset Bundle (+7,000 Assets) for Godot, Unreal and Unity</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/super-game-asset-bundle-7000-assets-for-godot-unreal-and-unity-software</link>
      <description>So many assets, so little time</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build your worlds with the Super Game Assets Bundle for Unreal, Godot, and Unity—featuring 7,000+ audio, visual, and environmental assets. This high-quality bundle features a truly diverse collection of themed assets ranging from medieval to cyberpunk. Create the next great RPG or action game with the Super Game Assets Bundle and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big Phat Music Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/big-phat-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Epic music for every creative endeavor</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the ultimate audioscape with Phat Phrog Studio's flagship bundle! This exclusive collection offers nearly 3,000 royalty-free tracks across 300+ music albums split into 86 genre-diverse asset packs, from RPG battle themes, mysterious survival melodies, heart pounding adrenaline action to chilled lo-fi beats. With 130+ hours of high-quality WAV files, including over 1,200 ambient tracks that are perfect for TTRPG's, this bundle has been developed over three years, valued at nearly $4,000. Game-ready and YouTube-friendly, it's everything you need for immersive soundscapes—all while supporting Direct Relief!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESIGN with CorelDRAW &amp; PERFECT with AI</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-with-coreldraw-perfect-with-ai-software</link>
      <description>CorelDRAW for novices and professionals</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master one of the most widely adapted design programs with our CorelDRAW 2024 Bundle. Get amazing software like <em>Corel Painter 2023</em>, <em>PaintShop Pro 2023</em>, and <em>Vision FX</em>. Learn professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD software options to design logos, posters, drafting, and more. Level up your creative skills and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Specialist - From Rookie to Pro</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/linux-specialist-from-rookie-to-pro-software</link>
      <description>Linux mastery is a bundle away</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Go from novice to expert in Linux with this comprehensive bundle that introduces users to the fundamentals in stages so students can truly master the operating system. Begin with the basics like the command line and progress into advanced skills like shell scripting, system management, and server administration. Explore cloud-based Linux environments, become proficient in system automation, and master Linux services in the cloud. Gain the expertise you need to become confident, powerful Linux professionals while supporting Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Squared Presents: Concept Art in Unreal Engine</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-squared-presents-concept-art-in-unreal-engine-software</link>
      <description>Master the basics of Unreal Engine</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to use one of the best video game engines in the industry with the ultimate Unreal Engine bundle from Learn Squared! This curriculum will help you level up your skills with courses like <em>Unreal Engine 5 Basics</em>, <em>Concept Art in Unreal Engine 5</em>, and more. You'll create vibrant, stylized environments and gain foundational skills in CGI filmmaking, making this bundle perfect for aspiring game artists, concept designers, and filmmakers. Familiarize yourself with Unreal Engine 5’s latest tools like Nanite and Lumen too. Get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>