<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 22:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Game Dev Asset Mega Bundle: Unreal Engine &amp; Unity</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/gamedev-asset-mega-bundle-unreal-engine-unity-software</link>
      <description>Gamedev assets for any situation</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bring the worlds in your imagination to life in Unity and Unreal Engine with this mind-blowingly massive collection of environments, props, tools, and more! From sprawling cyberpunk dystopias to soul-stirring medieval villages, you’ll have the building blocks to create masterwork game environments that will transport your players. You’ll get over three dozen megapacks made up of modular assets that you can mix and match as you please, that utilize engine-native cutting-edge tools like Nanite and Lumen. Pay what you want for this indispensable toolkit and help support charity with your purchase.<br/><br/><iframe width="352" height="198" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MCWt7v1A_SI?si=PLSiqrZ1WoPlpSM6" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br/><br/><p style="color: #ef9741;">Keys for this bundle are redeemed on either the Epic Games Store or Unity Asset Store, dependent on title.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lonely Planet / uTalk Travel and Learn - New Year, New Language, New Destination</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/lonely-planet-utalk-travel-and-learn-new-year-new-language-new-destination-software</link>
      <description>Explore the world as an informed traveler</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn how to navigate far-off lands with grace and confidence using this bundle of books and courses from Lonely Planet and uTalk Travel! This comprehensive library will help you level up your skills in a variety of languages and will show you the best-kept secrets from around the world. Get hot Lonely Planet travel books like <em>Lonely Planet Japan</em>, <em>Lonely Planet France</em>, <em>Lonely Planet Argentina</em>, and more. Get the expert advice from professional travelers and the knowledge you seek, and help support the World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GetRekt Best Stream Overlays of 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/getrekt-best-stream-overlays-2024-software</link>
      <description>Create your own custom overlays</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LfJvyrNmjLs?si=uBZLygeYwz_HykmQ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Dedicated to the streaming lifestyle? We knew it—upgrade your Twitch streams with this amazing overlay bundle from GetRekt today! Get a gigantic selection of customizable overlays like the <em>Nano Black 3D Stream Overlays Package</em>, <em>Horror Stream Overlays Package</em>, <em>Stellar 3D Stream Overlays Package</em>, and more! Take your live streams to the next level with personalized touches of style using these elite overlays. Plus, your purchase helps support Girls Who Code. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Pro 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vegas-pro-2024-software</link>
      <description>Our best-selling Vegas Pro bundle is back!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Content creators, influencers, and other video savvy friends—we’ve curated the ultimate bundle for you. Get the Vegas Pro Bundle by MAGIX and take your video editing to the next level. You’ll get the renowned and easy to learn video editing package <em>VEGAS Pro Edit 21</em>, packed with sophisticated compositing features as well as integrated audio and effects. Also included is <em>SOUND FORGE Pro 17</em>, a powerhouse audio editing suite with extensive plugin support, designed to deliver flawless masters. Start using these, and other easy to learn video editing software today. Pay what you want for this astounding bundle and help Make A Wish with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lens Legends: The Ultimate Photographer&#39;s Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/lens-legends-ulimate-photographers-toolkit-software</link>
      <description>Edit like a legend of the lens</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your photo skills with The Ultimate Photographer’s Toolkit Bundle from Ashampoo! Perfect for seasoned photographers and hobbyists alike, enhance your knowledge in a variety of editing disciplines. Get the power of advanced editing software like <em>Ashampoo SHARPEN #5 Professionals</em>, <em>Ashampoo ZOOM #2 professional</em>, <em>Ashampoo HDR #10 professional</em>, and more. Become a Lens Legend—and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Smarter: The Low/No-Code Development Essentials</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/build-smarter-lownocode-development-essentials-software</link>
      <description>No code—no problem!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to build smarter with our hottest no-code software bundle from the experts at Packt! Perfect for experts and novices—get tools like <em>Power Automate - A Guide to Power Automate Desktop</em>, <em>MindStudio Mastery - Automate Workflows and Build Gen AI Apps</em>, and <em>The Complete Masterclass on PL-900 Certification</em>—and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IK Pro Sound Suite Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ik-pro-sound-suite-software-encore</link>
      <description>The ultimate music production bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take your music creation to the next level with the Ultimate Sound and Groove Workstation Bundle from IK Multimedia. Download over 600 GB of professional, genre-defining and genre-defying pianos, drums, guitars, bass, brass, orchestral instruments, organs, synthesizer sounds, and many premade loops, presets, and more. Get the sounds you need to bring your ideas to life and into the ears of millions, while supporting Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate 2D and 3D Artist Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-2d-and-3d-artist-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The ultimate artists&#39; software bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Animate and create art like a professional with the Ultimate 2D and 3D Artists Bundle from Graphixly LLC. Perfect for artists looking to break into gaming, and industry veterans alike, this amazing bundle will have you creating in 2D and 3D in no time! Get tools and software like <em>Moho Pro 12.5</em>, <em>Paintstorm Studio</em>, <em>Realistic Paint Studio</em>, and more—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase. Bring your creations to life today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Unreal Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-unreal-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unlock a universe of curated assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers and sound engineers, give your creations life with rich audio and vibrant visuals with our Ultimate Unreal Mega Bundle! This high-quality collection features a plethora of unique sounds and models for your environments, characters, soundtracks, and more for use in popular engines like Unreal. Get a gigantic bundle of assets to help bring your games to life and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blender Core Skills: The Ultimate Blender Basics Bundle Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/blender-core-skills-ultimate-blender-basics-bundle-remix-software</link>
      <description>Your Blender skills just got better</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the basics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie! This comprehensive curriculum will help you master the fundamentals of Blender with topics like <em>Fundamentals of Mesh Modeling</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Digital Sculpting</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Materials and Shading</em>, and more! Get the Ultimate Blenders Basics Bundle and take your skills to the next level with the expert advice and knowledge recorded in Blender 4.2 LTS. Help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!ics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev Market: Best of 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/gamedev-market-best-2024-software</link>
      <description>75+ assets to create endlessly</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build your worlds with this bundle of 75+ assets from GameDev Market! This massive collection features a diverse range of high-quality assets, including detailed tilesets, unique character sprites, huge music and sound effects packs, and so much more. Perfect for indie developers and seasoned studios alike, this bundle has everything you need to help bring your game to life, and help support The Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESIGN with CorelDRAW &amp; PERFECT with AI</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-with-coreldraw-perfect-with-ai-software</link>
      <description>CorelDRAW for novices and professionals</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master one of the most widely adapted design programs with our CorelDRAW 2024 Bundle. Get amazing software like <em>Corel Painter 2023</em>, <em>PaintShop Pro 2023</em>, and <em>Vision FX</em>. Learn professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD software options to design logos, posters, drafting, and more. Level up your creative skills and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>