<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate 2D and 3D Artist Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-2d-and-3d-artist-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The ultimate artists&#39; software bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Animate and create art like a professional with the Ultimate 2D and 3D Artists Bundle from Graphixly LLC. Perfect for artists looking to break into gaming, and industry veterans alike, this amazing bundle will have you creating in 2D and 3D in no time! Get tools and software like <em>Moho Pro 12.5</em>, <em>Painstorm Studio</em>, <em>Realistic Paint Studio</em>, and more—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase. Bring your creations to life today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leartes Unreal and Unity Assets Giga Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/leartes-unreal-and-unity-assets-giga-bundle-software-encore2024</link>
      <description>Total asset madness for Unreal &amp; Unity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game devs, get ready—this mind-blowing bundle is about to exponentially explode the quantity of creative options at your disposal. Inside you’ll find dozens of asset packs, tools, and more, for Unreal Engine and Unity, ready to plug into your projects and accelerate your process of game creation. You’ll get a vast array of 3D models, textures, and interactive elements to help you craft stunning environments, from post-apocalyptic settings, to vibrant urban landscapes. Also included are fully-rigged characters and creatures, drivable and animated vehicles, sound and visual effect packs, and much, much more. Pay what you want for this vast interactive toolkit and help support Code.org with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Security: Zero to Hero Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cyber-security-zero-to-hero-bundle-software-encore</link>
      <description>Take your cybersecurity into your own hands</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking to skill-up into the exciting field of cybersecurity? Or do you simply want to keep your systems secure and hack-proof? This bundle of online courses from ACI Learning will arm you with the skills you need! Dive into the deep end with a course on the National Institute of Standards and Technology’s cybersecurity and risk management frameworks. Work toward CompTIA certifications including CASP+, CySA+, PenTest+, and Security+. Dive into specialized training with Cisco's CCNP Security, DevNet Associate, and more. Master ethical hacking with CEH v.12, enhance your risk management skills with CISM, CRISC, and NIST frameworks, and become a cybersecurity all-rounder ready to tackle any threat. Update your skillset with the tools you need to break into this thriving field and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Unreal Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-unreal-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unlock a universe of curated assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers and sound engineers, give your creations life with rich audio and vibrant visuals with our Ultimate Unreal Mega Bundle! This high-quality collection features a plethora of unique sounds and models for your environments, characters, soundtracks, and more for use in popular engines like Unreal. Get a gigantic bundle of assets to help bring your games to life and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blender Core Skills: The Ultimate Blender Basics Bundle Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/blender-core-skills-ultimate-blender-basics-bundle-remix-software</link>
      <description>Your Blender skills just got better</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the basics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie! This comprehensive curriculum will help you master the fundamentals of Blender with topics like <em>Fundamentals of Mesh Modeling</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Digital Sculpting</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Materials and Shading</em>, and more! Get the Ultimate Blenders Basics Bundle and take your skills to the next level with the expert advice and knowledge recorded in Blender 4.2 LTS. Help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!ics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animate Everything 3D with Anything World</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/animate-everything-3d-with-anything-world-software</link>
      <description>Generate and Animate in 3D</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your 3D asset creation, animation and world building skills with this amazing bundle from Anything World! Generate and animate hundreds of 3D models and bring your imagination to life! Learn to create in 3D with tutorials to help you sharpen your skills with professional courses on: how to make a platform game in Unity, how to create ready made environments, and how to make an isometric game in Unity. Get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Friday Rust Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/black-friday-rust-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Shake off the Rust on Black Friday</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn Rust with this bundle of courses from Zenva! This comprehensive curriculum will help you level up your skills with courses like <em>Learn Rust Programming for Beginners</em>, <em>Rust Web App Project - Real-Time Video Broadcasting</em>, <em>Build Your First Game with Rust and Bevy</em>, and more. Get expert advice from the pros and the knowledge you seek. Master one of the premier general-purpose programming languages, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocal Master Collection - Acapellas, Loops &amp; Plugins For Music Production &amp; Game Design</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vocal-master-collection-acapellas-loops-plugins-for-music-production-game-design-software</link>
      <description>A new music bundle? Sounds nice!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[This comprehensive audio bundle includes popular WA Production collections like <em>Vocal Compressor</em>, <em>Mutant Reverb</em>, and more! Create breathtaking soundscapes, master intricate vocal effects, and produce tracks across any genre with ease using an expansive range of professional tools and vocal libraries. From lush vocal harmonies to gritty shouts, this collection is packed with endless possibilities. Perfect for seasoned producers, sound designers, and creators who want to push boundaries and produce studio-quality projects with unparalleled creativity. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACI - Professional Developer: Easy Steps To Mastery</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/aci-professional-developer-easy-steps-to-mastery-software</link>
      <description>Elite tools for pro developers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Professional developers—level up your skills with this comprehensive bundle of courses including <em>Intro to Docker</em>, <em>Intro to NodeJS</em>, <em>HTML5 Canvas Graphics and Animations</em>, and more! Improve your skills in Java, NumPy, HTML5, and other programs pros use every day. Become a subject matter expert in a variety of fields and advance your career—get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Unreal Engine Sci-Fi Creators Kit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-unreal-engine-scifi-creators-kit-software</link>
      <description>Far out assets for Unreal Engine </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build amazing dream worlds with the Ultimate Unreal Engine Sci-Fi Creators Kit! This high-quality collection features environments, characters, meshes, models, animations, music, SFX, and more for use in Unreal Engine. Access assets for alien soldiers, sci-fi railroads, and other out of this world creators. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapelab Creator&#39;s Kit: 3D &amp; VR Sculpting Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/shapelab-creators-kit-software</link>
      <description>3D design at your fingertips</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create high-quality 3D models from the palms of your hands with the Shapelab 3D Bundle from Leopoly! This high-quality collection features a <em>Shapelab 2024</em> license, a voucher for the 2025 edition, and more! Create 3D dragons, dinosaurs, and other mysterious creatures with this awesome bundle. Get the assets you need to help bring your creations to life, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monument Studios: TTRPG Audio Compendium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/monument-studios-ttrpg-audio-compendium-software</link>
      <description>A bundle bursting with amazing music</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with this bundle of royalty-free sounds from Monument Studios! This massive library features loops, samples, one-shots, instruments, and others for a variety of genres & styles. Amazing collections like <em>Battle Music Vol 1 & 2</em>, <em>Fantasy Music Vol 1</em>, <em>Cinematic Hits</em>, and more. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev Market: Best of 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/gamedev-market-best-2024-software</link>
      <description>75+ assets to create endlessly</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build your worlds with this bundle of 75+ assets from GameDev Market! This massive collection features a diverse range of high-quality assets, including detailed tilesets, unique character sprites, huge music and sound effects packs, and so much more. Perfect for indie developers and seasoned studios alike, this bundle has everything you need to help bring your game to life, and help support The Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESIGN with CorelDRAW &amp; PERFECT with AI</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-with-coreldraw-perfect-with-ai-software</link>
      <description>CorelDRAW for novices and professionals</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master one of the most widely adapted design programs with our CorelDRAW 2024 Bundle. Get amazing software like <em>Corel Painter 2023</em>, <em>PaintShop Pro 2023</em>, and <em>Vision FX</em>. Learn professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD software options to design logos, posters, drafting, and more. Level up your creative skills and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>