<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Blender Core Skills: The Ultimate Blender Basics Bundle Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/blender-core-skills-ultimate-blender-basics-bundle-remix-software</link>
      <description>Your Blender skills just got better</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the basLearn the basics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie! This comprehensive curriculum will help you master the fundamentals of Blender with topics like <em>Fundamentals of Mesh Modeling</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Digital Sculpting</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Materials and Shading</em>, and more! Get the Ultimate Blenders Basics Bundle and take your skills to the next level with the expert advice and knowledge recorded in Blender 4.2 LTS. Help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!ics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie! This comprehensive curriculum will help you master the fundamentals of Blender with topics like <em>Fundamentals of Mesh Modeling</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Digital Sculpting</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Materials and Shading</em>, and more! Get the Ultimate Blenders Basics Bundle and take your skills to the next level with the expert advice and knowledge you seek. Help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete AWS, CompTIA, Azure,Google Cloud, and Cybersecurity Certification Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-aws-comptia-azuregoogle-cloud-and-cybersecurity-certification-bundle-software-encore</link>
      <description>AI tech certification &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Supercharge your resume and update your skillset with this bundle of online courses from Mammoth Interactive, with a focus on skills and certifications to get you ready to work in AI tech, cloud systems, security, IT, and more. You'll get 350+ hours of instruction to get you ready for valuable certifications, including Azure AI Engineer Associate, CompTIA Security+, Google Professional Machine Learning Engineer, AWS, and others. Also included are courses focused on cutting-edge skills, like building generative AI applications that take advantage of Google Cloud's suite of robust AI services. <strong>Every course comes with an unofficial sample practice test to help you prepare for the exam.</strong> Pay what you want for this bundle of career-boosting instruction and help support the Children's Miracle Network.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best of Synty Game Dev Assets #2 Remix Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/best-synty-game-dev-assets-2-remix-encore</link>
      <description>Build a low-poly wonderland</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bring your game to life with this massive bundle of distinctive, stylized low-poly 3D assets from Synty! You’ll get assets usable in Unity and Unreal to fit a wide spectrum of settings—everything from Ancient Rome and various flavors of the modern day, to far-future sci-fi! Included are dozens upon dozens of characters, buildings, interior and environmental props, special effects, and more. Craft grand Greek-inspired temples, neon-drenched urban nightclubs, and sleek, deadly starships, and people them memorable characters appropriate to their settings. Pay what you want for this jam-packed bundle and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase! <br/><br/>Keys and coupon must be redeemed by April 30th, 2025.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animate Everything 3D with Anything World</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/animate-everything-3d-with-anything-world-software</link>
      <description>Generate and Animate in 3D</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your 3D asset creation, animation and world building skills with this amazing bundle from Anything World! Generate and animate hundreds of 3D models and bring your imagination to life! Learn to create in 3D with tutorials to help you sharpen your skills with professional courses on: how to make a platform game in Unity, how to create ready made environments, and how to make an isometric game in Unity. Get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Friday Rust Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/black-friday-rust-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Shake off the Rust on Black Friday</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn Rust with this bundle of courses from Zenva! This comprehensive curriculum will help you level up your skills with courses like <em>Learn Rust Programming for Beginners</em>, <em>Rust Web App Project - Real-Time Video Broadcasting</em>, <em>Build Your First Game with Rust and Bevy</em>, and more. Get expert advice from the pros and the knowledge you seek. Master one of the premier general-purpose programming languages, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocal Master Collection - Acapellas, Loops &amp; Plugins For Music Production &amp; Game Design</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vocal-master-collection-acapellas-loops-plugins-for-music-production-game-design-software</link>
      <description>A new music bundle? Sounds nice!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[This comprehensive audio bundle includes popular WA Production collections like <em>Vocal Compressor</em>, <em>Mutant Reverb</em>, and more! Create breathtaking soundscapes, master intricate vocal effects, and produce tracks across any genre with ease using an expansive range of professional tools and vocal libraries. From lush vocal harmonies to gritty shouts, this collection is packed with endless possibilities. Perfect for seasoned producers, sound designers, and creators who want to push boundaries and produce studio-quality projects with unparalleled creativity. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACI - Professional Developer: Easy Steps To Mastery</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/aci-professional-developer-easy-steps-to-mastery-software</link>
      <description>Elite tools for pro developers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Professional developers—level up your skills with this comprehensive bundle of courses including <em>Intro to Docker</em>, <em>Intro to NodeJS</em>, <em>HTML5 Canvas Graphics and Animations</em>, and more! Improve your skills in Java, NumPy, HTML5, and other programs pros use every day. Become a subject matter expert in a variety of fields and advance your career—get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Unreal Engine Sci-Fi Creators Kit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-unreal-engine-scifi-creators-kit-software</link>
      <description>Far out assets for Unreal Engine </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build amazing dream worlds with the Ultimate Unreal Engine Sci-Fi Creators Kit! This high-quality collection features environments, characters, meshes, models, animations, music, SFX, and more for use in Unreal Engine. Access assets for alien soldiers, sci-fi railroads, and other out of this world creators. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapelab Creator&#39;s Kit: 3D &amp; VR Sculpting Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/shapelab-creators-kit-software</link>
      <description>3D design at your fingertips</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create high-quality 3D models from the palms of your hands with the Shapelab 3D Bundle from Leopoly! This high-quality collection features a <em>Shapelab 2024</em> license, a voucher for the 2025 edition, and more! Create 3D dragons, dinosaurs, and other mysterious creatures with this awesome bundle. Get the assets you need to help bring your creations to life, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAPS Extravaganza Revisited 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/maps-extravaganza-revisited-2024-software</link>
      <description>Bring your fantasy worlds to life</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Design maps for your own tabletop campaigns, fantasy settings, and more! This bundle includes everything you need to create stunning, print-worthy works of art that will bring your worlds to life. Get powerful software like Campaign Cartographer 3+ (including a Lifetime License), City Designer 3, Dungeon Designer 3, Tome of Ultimate Mapping, and more. Unlock a treasury that will take your tabletop games and fantasy stories to the next level, and help support Save the Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monument Studios: TTRPG Audio Compendium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/monument-studios-ttrpg-audio-compendium-software</link>
      <description>A bundle bursting with amazing music</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with this bundle of royalty-free sounds from Monument Studios! This massive library features loops, samples, one-shots, instruments, and others for a variety of genres & styles. Amazing collections like <em>Battle Music Vol 1 & 2</em>, <em>Fantasy Music Vol 1</em>, <em>Cinematic Hits</em>, and more. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2024 Learn Unity Game Development Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2024-learn-unity-game-development-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Get started in Unity today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to create games with Unity with these online courses from GameDev.tv! This comprehensive curriculum covers core skills and advanced concepts for the powerful and popular development platform. Find out how to make a 2D RPG combat system, VR experience, or turn-based strategy game. Get trained up on visual scripting, multiplayer, network coding, and more. Level up your Unity game dev skills, and help support Oceana with your purchase!<br><p>GameDev.tv have spent the last decade working with world class instructors to create the perfect learning experience for game development. Join our global community of over 2 million students and start making your own games today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev Market: Best of 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/gamedev-market-best-2024-software</link>
      <description>75+ assets to create endlessly</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build your worlds with this bundle of 75+ assets from GameDev Market! This massive collection features a diverse range of high-quality assets, including detailed tilesets, unique character sprites, huge music and sound effects packs, and so much more. Perfect for indie developers and seasoned studios alike, this bundle has everything you need to help bring your game to life, and help support The Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Game Asset Bundle (+7,000 Assets) for Godot, Unreal and Unity</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/super-game-asset-bundle-7000-assets-for-godot-unreal-and-unity-software</link>
      <description>So many assets, so little time</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build your worlds with the Super Game Assets Bundle for Unreal, Godot, and Unity—featuring 7,000+ audio, visual, and environmental assets. This high-quality bundle features a truly diverse collection of themed assets ranging from medieval to cyberpunk. Create the next great RPG or action game with the Super Game Assets Bundle and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESIGN with CorelDRAW &amp; PERFECT with AI</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-with-coreldraw-perfect-with-ai-software</link>
      <description>CorelDRAW for novices and professionals</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master one of the most widely adapted design programs with our CorelDRAW 2024 Bundle. Get amazing software like <em>Corel Painter 2023</em>, <em>PaintShop Pro 2023</em>, and <em>Vision FX</em>. Learn professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD software options to design logos, posters, drafting, and more. Level up your creative skills and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>