<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 23:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lens Legends: The Ultimate Photographer&#39;s Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/lens-legends-ulimate-photographers-toolkit-software</link>
      <description>Edit like a legend of the lens</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your photo skills with The Ultimate Photographer’s Toolkit Bundle from Ashampoo! Perfect for seasoned photographers and hobbyists alike, enhance your knowledge in a variety of editing disciplines. Get the power of advanced editing software like <em>Ashampoo SHARPEN #5 Professionals</em>, <em>Ashampoo ZOOM #2 professional</em>, <em>Ashampoo HDR #10 professional</em>, and more. Become a Lens Legend—and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dekogon Townscape Essentials - 2000+ Unreal Engine Assets Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/dekogon-townscape-essentials-2000-unreal-engine-assets-encore</link>
      <description>Open world in a box</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking to populate your Unreal Engine game world with eye-catching, true-to-life assets that are ready to plug into your workflow? This bundle has you covered. Included are a vast selection of packs full of the building blocks you need to create stunning small town environments, as well as vehicle models, props, and more—both Nanite-optimized and low-poly. You’ll get over 2000 assets in total, covering any sort of suburban scene your project might call for. Pay what you want and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blender Market: Best of 2024 Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/blender-market-best-2024-software-encore</link>
      <description>New Blender toys for artistic developers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, expand your world-building toolkit with this massive bundle of unique assets. This high-quality collection includes hard ops, terrain, liquids, humans, flora, and more for use in the renowned open-source development platform Blender. Get the assets you need to bring your game to life, and support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase. Don’t wait—start creating video games today! <br><p style="text-align: left;"><span style="color: #ff9900;"><strong>The assets in this bundle are final and will not undergo any further updates or revisions from the creators.</strong></span></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Smarter: The Low/No-Code Development Essentials</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/build-smarter-lownocode-development-essentials-software</link>
      <description>No code—no problem!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to build smarter with our hottest no-code software bundle from the experts at Packt! Perfect for experts and novices—get tools like <em>Power Automate - A Guide to Power Automate Desktop</em>, <em>MindStudio Mastery - Automate Workflows and Build Gen AI Apps</em>, and <em>The Complete Masterclass on PL-900 Certification</em>—and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deluxe Dev Dream: 3D Unreal Engine and Unity Mega Bundle 4000+ Assets Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/deluxe-dev-dream-3d-unreal-engine-and-unity-mega-bundle-4000-assets-software-encore</link>
      <description>Jaw-dropping environments for Unity &amp; Unreal</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iTx4D2PuibQ?si=nQKfIpVTTLeGefx8" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Get the tools you need to craft environments that will truly transport your players with this massive bundle of assets for Unity and Unreal Engine. Included are over 20 asset packs stuffed to the brim with modular architecture pieces, props, materials, textures, blueprints, and more. Whether you’re aiming for the majesty of feudal Japan or the grim darkness of a gothic dungeon, you’ll get all the building blocks you need to make your vision real. Plus, your purchase helps Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Survivors Flash Sale</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-survivors-flash-sale-software</link>
      <description>Bring brain eaters to life in Unreal</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build horrific or hilarious zombie worlds with the Unreal Survivors Flash Sale! Save cash on high-quality collections featuring a variety of zombie skins, animations, models, and more, alongside other amazing supporting assets for use in Unreal Engine. Create a variety of fun zombie scenarios limited only by your imagination. This Flash Sale Bundle is great for professionals or hobbyists looking to create in Unreal and save some money. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IK Pro Sound Suite Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ik-pro-sound-suite-software-encore</link>
      <description>The ultimate music production bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take your music creation to the next level with the Ultimate Sound and Groove Workstation Bundle from IK Multimedia. Download over 600 GB of professional, genre-defining and genre-defying pianos, drums, guitars, bass, brass, orchestral instruments, organs, synthesizer sounds, and many premade loops, presets, and more. Get the sounds you need to bring your ideas to life and into the ears of millions, while supporting Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate 2D and 3D Artist Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-2d-and-3d-artist-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The ultimate artists&#39; software bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Animate and create art like a professional with the Ultimate 2D and 3D Artists Bundle from Graphixly LLC. Perfect for artists looking to break into gaming, and industry veterans alike, this amazing bundle will have you creating in 2D and 3D in no time! Get tools and software like <em>Moho Pro 12.5</em>, <em>Painstorm Studio</em>, <em>Realistic Paint Studio</em>, and more—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase. Bring your creations to life today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Unreal Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-unreal-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unlock a universe of curated assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers and sound engineers, give your creations life with rich audio and vibrant visuals with our Ultimate Unreal Mega Bundle! This high-quality collection features a plethora of unique sounds and models for your environments, characters, soundtracks, and more for use in popular engines like Unreal. Get a gigantic bundle of assets to help bring your games to life and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blender Core Skills: The Ultimate Blender Basics Bundle Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/blender-core-skills-ultimate-blender-basics-bundle-remix-software</link>
      <description>Your Blender skills just got better</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the basics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie! This comprehensive curriculum will help you master the fundamentals of Blender with topics like <em>Fundamentals of Mesh Modeling</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Digital Sculpting</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Materials and Shading</em>, and more! Get the Ultimate Blenders Basics Bundle and take your skills to the next level with the expert advice and knowledge recorded in Blender 4.2 LTS. Help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!ics of Blender with this bundle of courses from CG Cookie!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animate Everything 3D with Anything World</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/animate-everything-3d-with-anything-world-software</link>
      <description>Generate and Animate in 3D</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your 3D asset creation, animation and world building skills with this amazing bundle from Anything World! Generate and animate hundreds of 3D models and bring your imagination to life! Learn to create in 3D with tutorials to help you sharpen your skills with professional courses on: how to make a platform game in Unity, how to create ready made environments, and how to make an isometric game in Unity. Get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Friday Rust Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/black-friday-rust-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Shake off the Rust on Black Friday</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn Rust with this bundle of courses from Zenva! This comprehensive curriculum will help you level up your skills with courses like <em>Learn Rust Programming for Beginners</em>, <em>Rust Web App Project - Real-Time Video Broadcasting</em>, <em>Build Your First Game with Rust and Bevy</em>, and more. Get expert advice from the pros and the knowledge you seek. Master one of the premier general-purpose programming languages, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocal Master Collection - Acapellas, Loops &amp; Plugins For Music Production &amp; Game Design</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vocal-master-collection-acapellas-loops-plugins-for-music-production-game-design-software</link>
      <description>A new music bundle? Sounds nice!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[This comprehensive audio bundle includes popular WA Production collections like <em>Vocal Compressor</em>, <em>Mutant Reverb</em>, and more! Create breathtaking soundscapes, master intricate vocal effects, and produce tracks across any genre with ease using an expansive range of professional tools and vocal libraries. From lush vocal harmonies to gritty shouts, this collection is packed with endless possibilities. Perfect for seasoned producers, sound designers, and creators who want to push boundaries and produce studio-quality projects with unparalleled creativity. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Unreal Engine Sci-Fi Creators Kit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-unreal-engine-scifi-creators-kit-software</link>
      <description>Far out assets for Unreal Engine </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build amazing dream worlds with the Ultimate Unreal Engine Sci-Fi Creators Kit! This high-quality collection features environments, characters, meshes, models, animations, music, SFX, and more for use in Unreal Engine. Access assets for alien soldiers, sci-fi railroads, and other out of this world creators. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>